anthonysfla.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy

## OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY

Welcome! Anthony’s Ladies Apparel is committed to protecting your personal information when you are using our website. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) is intended to explain what types of information we at Anthony’s Inc., doing business as Anthony’s Ladies Apparel (“Anthony’s”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) collect about you and how we use and share that information. [One section of this privacy policy also addresses what happens with information we collect on our pages on social media sites, such as Facebook, Instagram, and Pinterest (“Social Media Pages”)].

This Privacy Policy applies to the information collected when you use our website <http://www.anthonysfla.com/> (the “Site”), shop in our stores or otherwise interact with us as described below. Anthony’s will not collect, use or disclose your personal information other than in compliance with this Policy.

By using the [www.anthonysfla.com](http://www.anthonysfla.com/) website and/or making online purchases of product, you agree to the terms and conditions of Anthony’s Policy. If our Policy changes in the future, we will notify our customers and website users of any such changes by posting an updated Policy on our website.

Following the posting of such changes, your continued use of the [www.anthonysfla.com](http://www.anthonysfla.com/) website will constitute your acceptance of these changes and you will be bound by such changes. If you do not continue to use the [www.anthonysfla.com](http://www.anthonysfla.com/) website following a change to our Policy but take no other action with respect to your personal information, our use of that information will remain subject to our Policy as it was in effect prior to that change. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Policy and any changes thereto.

We offer you the ability to connect to our website or use our applications, services, and tools using a mobile device, either through a mobile application or via a mobile-optimized website. The provisions of this Policy apply to all such mobile access and use of mobile devices. The Policy will be referenced by all such mobile applications or mobile-optimized websites.

## Our Privacy Policy

SECTION 1 - WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION DOES ANTHONY’S COLLECT?

  1. Personal Information

We may ask you to provide personal information as part of the buying and selling process when you establish or update an account on the Site, sign up to receive emails from Anthony’s, search for a product, make a purchase from our store, interact with us by phone, email or through a web form, participate in sweepstakes, contests, promotions or surveys, join our Social Media Pages or through our mobile applications. We use this information to make your shopping experience as easy and enjoyable as possible.

Categories of personal information collected online include:

  * Your name – so we know what to call you.
  * Email address – so we can email you order confirmations, delivery delays, offers, etc.
  * Billing and shipping address information – so we can properly handle your order.
  * Names of people to whom purchases have been shipped – so that we may send orders to the proper recipient.
  * Credit card information – we only ask for this when you place an order.
  * A telephone number and/or mobile number – so we can call you when we have a question or problem with your order.
  * Product interest information – so that we may assist you in finding what you are looking for
  * Any other information you choose to provide – so we can customize your shopping experience.

This information is referred to as “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy. When you visit our website, we may gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include without limitation browser information, Internet Service Provider (ISP), operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or other device identifiers, location and date/time stamp.            

  2. General Browsing and Tracking Mechanisms

We gather navigational information about where visitors go on the Site and the information about the technical efficiencies of the Site (i.e. time to connect to our website, time to download pages, etc.) This information is referred to in this Privacy Policy as “Navigational Information” and allows us to see which areas of the site are most visited and helps us to better understand our visitor’s experience on the Site. In the process of gathering Navigational Information, non-personally identifiable information (i.e. domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address) may be collected with will provide information regarding a visitor’s use of the Site.

We collect Navigational Information from technology such as Cookies and Web Beacons.

Cookies are small text files that websites send to your computer. A cookie can be thought of as an Internet user’s identification card. Cookies help us to personalize the content of the Site, track visitors’ interest in our product and understand what most appeals to our customers so we can make our offers as appropriate as possible. Cookies are not computer programs and cannot read other information saved on your computer’s hard drive. **They cannot be used to disseminate viruses or get a user’s email address.**

By using our Site you consent to our placement of cookies on your computer. If you prefer, you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. However, if you turn your cookies off, some features of the site may not function properly.  Please note that cookies are computer specific, so if you log on to any site from a different computer, the cookie settings on that computer will apply.

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

 _session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).

 _shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits

 _shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.

cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.

 _secure_session_id, unique token, sessional

 storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

 PREF, persistent for a very short period, Set by Google and tracks who visits the store and from where

Web Beacons are small strings of code that are placed in a web page or email message to track your navigation on a website or collection of sites. They are sometimes called “clear GIFs” (Graphics Interchange Format) or “pixel tags”. Web beacons are used in conjunction with cookies to track activity on our Site, the completion of transaction and browsing behavior. When you visit a particular page, the web beacon will notify us of your visit. When used in email, web beacons enable us to know whether you have received the email.

  3. Social Media Sites and Pages

Personal Information may be collected directly by us through our Social Media Pages and may also be collected by the social media sites hosting our Social Media Pages.

Example of how Personal Information may be directly collected by us through our Social Media Pages include providing Personal Information through a form which has a link to this Privacy Policy. We will use and share the Personal Information we collect on or through our Social Media Pages in the manner specified below in WHAT DOES ANTHONY’S DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION and WHAT INFORMATION IS SHARED WITH THIRD-PARTY SERVICES.

The Social Media Sites may provide aggregate information and analysis to us about visitors’ use of our Social Media Pages. This allows us to better understand and analyze our user growth and collect general demographic information about the users of our Social Media Pages and their interaction with content on our Social Media Pages.

This Privacy Policy does not cover Personal Information collected by any Social Media Site or the privacy and security practices of any Social Media Site. Please review privacy policies and terms of service on the applicable Social Media Site if you have questions about their privacy or security practices.  

SECTION 2 - WHAT DOES ANTHONY’S DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

We use your information to:

  * Process your order and answer questions about the status of your order.
  * Send you or your friends, relatives or associates products that you have ordered.
  * Maintain contact with you or the product recipient(s) in the event of order delay or difficulty.
  * Deliver information through various communication channels you have provided to us about our product or the Site, including adding you to our email list or to our customer phone and mail marketing lists when you register for an account or make a purchase.
  * Send information about events, surveys, promotions, contests, products and other updates to you.
  * Tailor your experience on the Site to your interests.
  * Develop and improve our products, services, and the Site.
  * Respond to your inquiries.

If you have set up an account on the Site, you may save your Personal Information securely in that Account and we will access this Personal Information to make your shopping quicker and easier. We require you to create and/or access your Account to use various features of the Site, such as accessing your order history.

With respect to emails, we will use your Personal Information to send you exclusive information about special offers, events, new products and much more. If at any time you would like to stop future delivery of emails from us, please follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of each email. Please note, however, that your request not to receive email information will not preclude us from contacting you by email or otherwise regarding questions we have about your purchase and other operational emails, such as order confirmation or shipping emails.

We use the Personal information collected on our Social Media Pages to send communications regarding our products, services, and promotions; to respond to inquiries; to conduct surveys, sweepstakes or contest; to analyze your activity on our Social Media Pages and to develop our product and service offerings.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. We use cookies, web beacons and other tracking technology to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about the Site’s traffic and interaction so that we can offer better experiences and tools in the future.

As provided below, you may always choose not to receive promotional materials or marketing information.

SECTION 3 – CONSENT

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us.

  1. How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

  2. How do I access or change my personal information or withdraw my consent?

Anthony’s will ensure that the personal information it collects is as accurate, complete and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is being used. You are entitled to request access to and provide correction of your personal information collected by us. If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by following the removal instructions located at the bottom of each email or contacting us at [customerservice@anthonysfla.com](mailto:customerservice@anthonysfla.com), calling us at 1-800-324-1380 or write to us at:

> Anthony's Ladies Apparel, Customer Service, P.O. Box 18769, West Palm Beach, FL 33416

To opt out of our direct mail (mailers, catalogs, postcards, etc.), please contact us using any of the methods listed above. 

  3. California Privacy Rights

California residents who have established business relationships with us, under the California law, may request certain information about our disclosure of Personal Information during the prior calendar year or may choose to opt out of sharing their Personal Information with third parties. To make such a request, please send us an email at [customerservice@anthonysfla.com](mailto:customerservice@anthonysfla.com) with the words “California Privacy Rights” in the subject line or write to us at:

> Anthony's Ladies Apparel, Customer Service, P.O. Box 18769, West Palm Beach, FL 33416

SECTION 4 - WHAT INFORMATION IS SHARED WITH THIRD-PARTY SERVICES?

We may contract with reputable third-party service providers who perform services on our behalf (“Third Party Vendors”). In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. We do not sell or rent your personal information to non-affiliated third parties.

We currently use the services of a few carefully selected companies to help manage and optimize our Internet and retail businesses. Some examples of the assistance that may be provided by third-party service providers are: monitoring and analyzing Site activity, operations and marketing assistance, hosting the Site, processing orders, running promotions, events, and surveys, maintaining our database, administering and monitoring emails. We will share your Personal Information with these Third Party Vendors only as necessary for them to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law. Use of your Information by these Third Party Vendors is governed by their own privacy policies and procedures and not by this Privacy Policy.

We may share your Information with any of our parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures or other company under common control with us. As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, sale of assets, dissolution, or similar event, we may transfer or disclose your personal information to a purchaser or prospective purchaser, who may collect, use and disclose such information for the purposes of evaluating the proposed transaction or operating and managing the affairs of the acquired business, or for other purposes identified in this Policy.

To the extent permitted by law, we may also disclose Information when required by law, court order or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency, or whenever we believe that disclosing such information is necessary or advisable, for example, to protect the rights, property or safety of us or others.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our Site’s Terms of Service.

SECTION 5 - DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

SECTION 6 - RETENTION OF INFORMATION

We will keep your personal information only as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Policy or such longer period as may be required by applicable law.

SECTION 7 - SHOPIFY

Our store is hosted by Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you. Your data is stored in Shopify’s data storage, databases, and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (http://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement (http://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).

SECTION 8 - SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. Furthermore, each and every ALDO employee, mandatory or agent must abide by this Policy.               

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

SECTION 9 – MOBILE PRIVACY

When you use our mobile optimized website or our mobile application, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. Anthony’s and our service providers may use and store this information to provide you with location-based services, search results, and other personalized content. Anthony’s will provide notifications only to those customers who accept to receive such notifications. Most mobile devices allow you to control or disable location services in this device’s settings menu. If you have questions about how to disable your device’s location services, we recommend that you contact your mobile service carrier or the manufacturer of your particular device.

SECTION 10 – PHOTO SHARING POLICY #MYANTHONYS or @ANTHONYSFLA

Thank you for sharing your photo with Anthony’s using our hashtag #myanthonys or by tagging us @anthonysfla. If we like your photo we want to share it on our social media sites, we would first need your permission to use the photo. If you provide us with that permission, you would be agreeing to our terms of service for photo sharing.

SECTION 11 - AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

Anthony’s does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. Those under age 13 should not use Anthony’s website or provide Anthony’s with any personal information.

SECTION 12 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at [customerservice@anthonysfla.com](mailto:customerservice@anthonysfla.com) or by mail at:

Anthony's Ladies Apparel

Privacy Compliance Officer

P.O. Box 18769

West Palm Beach, FL 33416

Last Updated: June 5, 2018

\----
